Jeferson Arboleda Gómez

C/Santiago, 16, Albacete, Spain * (34) 678 20 83 13 * me@jarboleda.me * https://www.jarboleda.me/

SUMMARY

Aug 1992, Colombia. Software Engineer located in Spain since 2002. Half year experience on helpdesk environments and 1+ year experience as full stack web developer. Went back to university to improve my skills with a master's degree and now I am looking for a challenging job.

CORE COMPETENCIES

- Self-motivated
- Detailed and organized

- Determined
- Full lifecycle software development

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programming	Python, JavaScript, bash, PHP, SASS, Java
Platforms	IBM Bluemix, Docker, Kubernetes, Google App Engine
Environments	Linux (Fedora, Ubuntu), macOS X, Windows

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

TCSET

Lead developer, Jan 2016 - Sep 2016

- Managed 5+ projects from requirements through successful deployment and maintenance.
- Set goals and deadlines for the department.
- Worked with other departments to ensure project completions in time.
- Reengineered internal processes to improve operations, such as deployments.
- Mentored an intern in day to day operations.

TCSET

Developer, Jul 2015 - Dec 2015

- Assisted in the development of web (front end) and mobile apps for multiple clients.
- Participated in staff meetings, providing updates on my tasks.

TCSET

Internship, Jan 2015 - Jul 2015

- Provided customer support and remote assistance.
- Contributed to manage company's dedicated servers (4).
- Contributed to domain management (100+) and migrations between providers.

EDUCATION

University of Castilla-La Mancha, ES

Degree in Computer Engineering, 2011 - 2015

University of Castilla-La Mancha, ES

Master in Computer Engineering, 2016 - 2017

Cambridge ESOL

Certificate in Advanced English (C1), 2017

LANGUAGES

Spanish (Native language)

English (Advanced - C1)

ADDITIONAL DATA

- Willing to relocate
- LinkedIn
- GitHub